<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to Zhaohui&#39;s research website! on QualityDream Lab</title>
    <link>https://zhaohuigeng.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome to Zhaohui&#39;s research website! on QualityDream Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://zhaohuigeng.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://zhaohuigeng.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaohuigeng.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About the QualityDream Lab  The QualityDream stands for Quality Design for Reverse Engineering and Additive Manufacturing. The overarching goal of Zhaohui Research Group (ZRG) is to develop an architecture, both in establishing the theory and in developing methodology, which provides complete access to spatial data and can execute analytical methodologies to achieve various research and production objectives.
About Me  My name is Zhaohui Geng. I am currently an Assistant Professor (tenure-track) in the Department of Manufacturing and Industrial Engineering at The University of Texas Rio Grande Valley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Group</title>
      <link>https://zhaohuigeng.github.io/group/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaohuigeng.github.io/group/</guid>
      <description>Faculty
Zhaohui Geng
2016-2021, Ph.D. in Industrial Engineering, University of Pittsburgh
2016-2018, M.A. in Statistics, University of Pittsburgh
2014-2016, M.S. in Industrial Engineering, University of Pittsburgh
2010-2014, B.E. in Electronic Science and Technology, Nankai University
   Graduate Students
  TBA
  Undergraduate Students
  TBA
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publication and Presentation</title>
      <link>https://zhaohuigeng.github.io/publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaohuigeng.github.io/publication/</guid>
      <description>Please see my CV or Google Scholar for the complete list.
Recent Journal Publications (Published/Under Review) Geng, Z. and Bidanda, B. (2021) Utilizing Dual Functionalities of Reverse Engineering in Additive Manufacturing: Metrology and Quality Implications. Submitted to Manufacturing Letters.
Geng, Z., Sabbaghi, A., and Bidanda, B. (2021). Reconstructing Original Design: Process Planning for Reverse Engineering. Revision at IISE Transactions. 
Geng, Z., Sabbaghi, A., and Bidanda, B. (2021). A Framework of Tolerance Specification for Freeform Point Clouds and Capability Analysis for Reverse Engineering Processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://zhaohuigeng.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaohuigeng.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>The University of Texas Rio Grande Valley
Graduate Courses (Lecturer) TBA
Undergraduate Courses (Lecturer) TBA
University of Pittsburgh
Undergraduate Courses (Lecturer)  ENGR-0020 Probability and Statistics for Engineers I (SPRING 2018, Fall 2018, Fall 2020, Spring 2021)  Graduate Courses (Teaching Assistant):  IE-2062 Data Mining (Spring 2020) IE-2007 Statistics and Data Analysis (Spring 2020) IE-1089/2089 Additive Manufacturing (Summer 2018)  Undergraduate Courses (Teaching Assistant)  IE-1082 Probabilistic Methods in Operations Research (Summer 2020) IE-1089/2089 Additive Manufacturing (Summer 2018)      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Zhaohui&#39;s research website!</title>
      <link>https://zhaohuigeng.github.io/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaohuigeng.github.io/home/</guid>
      <description>Zhaohui Geng Assistant Professor
Department of Manufacturing and Industrial Engineering
The University of Texas Rio Grande Valley
 Contact Information Department of Manufacturing and Industrial Engineering
The University of Texas Rio Grande Valley
1201 West University Drive
Edinburg, TX 78539
Office: TBA
E-mail: zhaohui dot geng at utrgv dot edu
Phone: (412) 944-7917
    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
